Hi everyone, my name is Joshua,
नमस्ते सभी को, मेरा नाम जोशुआ है,
co-founder of Overseez, and today I'm going to quickly show you how to use
Overseez का सह-संस्थापक, और आज मैं आपको जल्दी से दिखाऊंगा कि हमारी
our website. So first, on the homepage,
वेबसाइट का उपयोग कैसे करें। तो सबसे पहले, होमपेज पर,
you're going to see this button, Try AI Now,
आपको यह बटन दिखेगा, Try AI Now,
you're going to press that. The search bar here,
आपको उसे दबाना है। यहाँ सर्च बार है,
where you can look at anything you want, whether it's products,
जहाँ आप अपनी पसंद की कोई भी चीज़ खोज सकते हैं, चाहे वह उत्पाद हों,
services, or places, you can also change your location and currency
सेवाएँ हों, या स्थान, आप किसी भी समय अपनी लोकेशन और करेंसी भी बदल सकते हैं,
at any time, so everything is personalized to where you are.
ताकि सब कुछ आपकी जगह के हिसाब से पर्सनलाइज्ड हो।
So right here, if you click this button, Refresh, you'll change your location,
तो यहाँ, यदि आप इस बटन, Refresh पर क्लिक करते हैं, तो आप अपनी लोकेशन बदल लेंगे,
and right here, you can change your currency. So right now,
और यहाँ से, आप अपनी करेंसी बदल सकते हैं। तो अभी,
I'm going to change to Canadian dollars because I'm located in Canada,
मैं कनाडाई डॉलर में बदल रहा हूँ क्योंकि मैं कनाडा में हूँ,
and you can search anything you want. Let's try apple juice.
और आप अपनी पसंद की कोई भी चीज़ खोज सकते हैं। चलिए सेब का जूस (apple juice) ट्राई करते हैं।
I want to buy apple juice,
मैं सेब का जूस खरीदना चाहता हूँ,
and one of our best features is that you can enter your bank name
और हमारी सबसे अच्छी विशेषताओं में से एक यह है कि आप अपने बैंक का नाम दर्ज कर सकते हैं
to instantly see the fees you would pay abroad. So I'm going to enter my bank
ताकि आप विदेश में भुगतान की जाने वाली फीस तुरंत देख सकें। तो मैं अपने बैंक
name, and I'm going to type in my details
का नाम दर्ज करूँगा, और मैं अपनी जानकारी टाइप करूँगा
and see how much I can save
और देखूँगा कि मैं कितनी बचत कर सकता हूँ
on each purchase right away. So right here we can see our five options.
प्रत्येक खरीद पर तुरंत। तो यहाँ हम अपने पाँच विकल्प देख सकते हैं।
You can see the price, you can see the overseas fee you would pay
आप कीमत देख सकते हैं, आप वह ओवरसीज फीस देख सकते हैं जो आप भुगतान करेंगे
with your card, the average price of the area of the product,
अपने कार्ड से, उस क्षेत्र में उत्पाद की औसत कीमत,
and how much you're saving. So right here the average of an apple
और आप कितनी बचत कर रहे हैं। तो यहाँ एक सेब के जूस का औसत
juice is three dollars twenty five,
तीन डॉलर पच्चीस सेंट है,
but with our AI you found a discount and it only cost
लेकिन हमारे AI के साथ आपको एक डिस्काउंट मिला और इसकी कीमत केवल
one dollar twenty seven, so you'd be saving one dollar ninety four.
एक डॉलर सत्ताईस सेंट है, तो आप एक डॉलर चौरानवे सेंट बचा रहे होंगे।
So how does it work? You just go here. You like this.
तो यह कैसे काम करता है? आप बस यहाँ जाएँ। आपको यह पसंद आया।
This option Walmart, you click here.
यह विकल्प Walmart, आप यहाँ क्लिक करें।
I saved here and you click log saving.
मैंने यहाँ बचत की और आप log saving पर क्लिक करें।
So as you can see, it's already saved.
तो जैसा कि आप देख सकते हैं, यह पहले ही सेव हो चुका है।
And here at this bottom view on maps, if you like something,
और यहाँ नीचे view on maps पर, यदि आपको कुछ पसंद आता है,
you just click the button and it'll take you directly to Google Maps.
तो आप बस बटन पर क्लिक करें और यह आपको सीधे Google Maps पर ले जाएगा।
So you can easily get there. And now we go to our
ताकि आप आसानी से वहाँ पहुँच सकें। और अब हम अपने
dashboard and you'll see a progress bar that tracks how much money you've saved
डैशबोर्ड पर जाते हैं और आपको एक प्रोग्रेस बार दिखाई देगा जो ट्रैक करता है कि आपने कितने पैसे बचाए हैं
using our AI and our discounts.
हमारे AI और हमारे डिस्काउंट का उपयोग करके।
And right here in recent savings, you can also keep track of everything you've
और यहाँ recent savings में, आप अपनी बचत की गई हर चीज़ का
been saving, including the place right here,
हिसाब रख सकते हैं, जिसमें यहाँ स्थान,
the date and the exact amount all in one spot.
तारीख और सटीक राशि सब एक ही जगह पर है।
So that's it. It's really simple, fast and built to help you save smarter
तो बस इतना ही। यह Overseez के साथ स्मार्ट तरीके से बचत करने में आपकी मदद करने के लिए
with Overseez. Thank you guys.
बाकी सब बहुत सरल, तेज़ और निर्मित है। धन्यवाद दोस्तों।